

Md Samim Akhter

Professional Freelancer

mdsamimakhter2001@gmail.com

Abinashpur, Birbhum, India

_

linkedin.com/in/md-samim-akhter

. .

facebook.com/imdsamimakhter

Hello, Myself Md Samim Akhter, a 22-year-old individual with in-depth knowledge of Search Engine and Creative Writing, is a highly motivated and skilled person. I'm passionate about social justice and making a positive impact in the society, and I'm excited to see what the future holds.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Professional Freelancer

Appen

01/2023 - Present

Copywriting, SEO, Content Writing, Annotation, Social Media, Data Collection

Search Engine Evaluator (Freelance)

Welocalize.inc

02/2023 - 07/2023 SEO, UX and Quality Auditor,

Google Ads

Content Writing/Blogging

Google Blogger & WordPress

2020 - 2022

Customer Service

Rinku Electronics

2017 - 2022

Resolving queries regarding products and services

EDUCATION

Computer Science and Engineering in Al & Machine Learning

St. Mary's Technical Campus

2023 - Present Barasat, Kolkata

Diploma in Computer Science and Technology

Santiniketan Institute of Polytechnic

08/2020 - 07/2023 Muluk, Birbhum

Bachelor of Arts (BA)

Birbhum Mahavidyalaya

08/2020 - 07/2023 Suri , Birbhum

Senior Secondary Education (10th+2)

Abinashpur High School

05/2018 - 03/2020 Abinashpur, Birbhum

Secondary Education (10th)

Abinashpur High School

01/2016 - 01/2020 Abinashpur, Birbhum

SKILLS



COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Data Analyst Course certified by LinkedIn (08/2023)

Python Fundamental Course by Great Learning (08/2023)

Machine Learning & Data Science with Python-Intership (03/2023 - 06/2023)

PHN Technology Pvt. Ltd.

Community Influencing Internship at InAmigos Foundation (11/2022 - 12/2022)

IT/ITES (NSDC) NSQF L.v-4 (01/2016 - 12/2019)
Abinashpur High School

Diploma in Information Technology Application (DITA) (04/2018 - 04/2019)

Panrui Youth Computer Training Centre

Tally ERP 9 Training (04/2019 - 10/2019)

Panrui Youth Computer Training Centre

LANGUAGES

English	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Bengali	\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet
Hindi	\bullet \bullet \circ \circ

INTERESTS

Cycling, Painting, Reading and Listening Stories, Playing Football, Volley, Carrom, Puzzle Solving, Online Games and many more.